

MUHAMMAD ALIMIE BIN ROSLI SOFTWARE ENGINEER

a junior programmer experienced with web application development. Developed and maintained system with various modules for multiple projects. Love to explore any new language, frameworks or skills related to either web app, mobile app or desktop app development.

LANGUAGES

Bahasa Malaysia	
	EXCELLENT
English	
	GOOD

SKILLS

- Java, Spring Framework
- Angular 2+
- PHP, Laravel Framework
- Javascript & Jquery
- HTML5 & CSS3
- -
- BootstrapMySQL
- Git, SVN
- JIRA
- Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop

REFERENCES

NAWAAL ISHAK (TEAM LEAD)

MIMOS Berhad nawaal.ishak@mimos.my +6017 - 310 1817

MUHAMMAD UZZAIR (AST. MANAGER)

Datakraf Solution SDN BHD uzzair@datakraf.com +6013 - 378 8484

DR. HAYATI ABD RAHMAN (LECTURER)

Universiti teknologi MARA hayatiar@tmsk.uitm.edu.my +603 - 5521 1123 Sungai Buloh, Selangor



+6014 - 715 9204



in muhammadalimie

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

JUL 2019 - JUL 2020

MIMOS Berhad

- Involved in development of Food Safety System Malaysia (FoSIM) for Ministry of Health Malaysia (KKM).
- Responsible for backend development using Java Spring framework and frontend development using Angular 2+ framework for every module assigned.
- Developed and maintained 2 modules including registration module (company & premise management) and labeling module (food labeling application).
- Designed, implemented and maintained the database for each module using MySQL.
- Contributed in angular components development for every assigned module.
- Exposed with the use of microservices architecture which is developed for FoSIM.
- Involved in module development using agile development cycle.
- Collaborated closely with all team members to deliver each task in time with help of various tech tools including JIRA, Fisheye and Slack.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

JAN 2018 - JUN 2019

Datakraf Solution SDN BHD

- Involved in both backend and frontend system development for every module assigned by applying HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery, Bootstrap, and PHP.
- Designed, implemented and maintained system databases for small to medium scale projects (MySQL).
- Developed and maintained web application such as Human Resource Management System (HRMS) and Membership System using PHP Laravel framework.
- Assigned and developed more than 6 modules in HR Management System including Staff, Leave, Claim, Directory, Meeting, Asset Booking and Medical Management.
- Developed and Involved with integration of payment gateway such as ipay88 and FPX into payment system using PHP Laravel Framework.
- Designed and developed multiple static websites including corporate websites and landing page for prototype version and for production.
- Developed multiple e-Commerce websites with Opencart CMS.
- Managed cloud server (Ubuntu) for multiple project from development to production deployment using Digital Ocean (Droplets).
- Experienced with Nginx and Apache2 web server for websites hosting, plus CDN using Cloudflare to increase websites security.
- Experienced in managing project using control version (Git) with Gitlab and GitHub.
- Experienced with project management tools using Trello and Slack.
- Managed task related to multimedia such as graphic and video editing using Adobe CS such as Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop and Premier Pro.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE (HONS) MULTIMEDIA COMPUTING

2014 - 2018

Universiti Teknologi MARA (UiTM) Shah Alam

- Graduated on July 2018 with CGPA 3.32, Computer Science Multimedia Computing.
- Developed native android app for mobile data security using java (Final Year Project)
- Excellent grade point in all programming courses including C++, Java and Javascript.
- Studied human-computer interaction (Websites) and applied for UI & UX using markup language such as HTML, HTML5 and CSS3.
- Trained to handle various tools in managing static and temporal media through multimedia programming and using Adobe Creative Suite.